# PABLO POCOSTALES

Filmmaker // Video Editor // Graphic Designer

#### **PROFILE**

Date of birth: Nov 1989

I consider myself a professional filmmaker with extensive experience in camera operation, sound equipment, and scene lighting. I completed my studies in 2012, and since then, I have been continuously specializing and furthering my education in the audiovisual field up to the present day.

## **EXPERIENCE**

Filmmaker & Multimedia Designer

Deloitte // Luxembourg

Nov 2018 - present

Video filming and editing for the branding department.

Creation of motion design and promotional videos for social media.

Filmmaker & Graphic Designer

Freelancer // Spain

Apr 2017 - Nov 2018

Video creation and editing, logo design and development, catalog layout for web pagination, and social media

Cameraman & Video Editor

Alcor Extremadura Raid // Spain

Mar 2013 - Apr 2016 Recording and editing of promotional videos for social networks.

Videomaker & Production

MediaUni Web - UV // Spain

Nov 2011 - May 2012

Cameraman, video editor, developer and creator of a Sport program for the official web page of University of Valencia.

Camera Assistant

VAV Productions // Spain

Jul 2011 - Sept 2012 Camera assistant in a live program of Canal Extremadura TV.

# **EDUCATION**

Sept 2007 - Sept 2011

Bachelor of Audiovisual Communication

University of Extremadura

Nov 2011 - May 2012 Master's Degree in Audiovisuals Contents and Formats University of Valencia

# **VOLUNTARY WORKS**

2014

Bulgaria // International Short Films Festival as a film assistant

2015

Macedonia // EuroHandball Women Sub-17 as a cameraman and video editor

2016

Czech Republic // Training Course Video Editing

#### PRO. SKILLS

PHOTOSHOP

ILLUSTRATOR

PREMIERE PRO

AFTER EFFECTS

FINAL CUT

INDESIGN

ANIMATE

#### **EXPERTISE**

RECORDING

VIDEO EDITING

PHOTOGRAPHY

GRAPHIC DESIGN

# PER. SKILLS

CREATIVE

TEAM WORK

COMMUNICATIVE

## LANGUAGES

SPANISH

**ENGLISH** 

GERMAN